{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780881816","data":{"timestamp":" 946780881816"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780893470","data":{"timestamp":" 946780893469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780894368","data":{"timestamp":" 946780894368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780895030","data":{"timestamp":" 946780895029"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780895652","data":{"timestamp":" 946780895651"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780895871","data":{"timestamp":" 946780895871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780896615","data":{"timestamp":" 946780896615"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" DASARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780899609","data":{"timestamp":" 946780899609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780900895","data":{"timestamp":" 946780900895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALIMNUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780901489","data":{"timestamp":" 946780901489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINTU"," userResponse":" CHINTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780902251","data":{"timestamp":" 946780902251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780902326","data":{"timestamp":" 946780902326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780903320","data":{"timestamp":" 946780903320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780905842","data":{"timestamp":" 946780905842"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780907611","data":{"timestamp":" 946780907611"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALININUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALININUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780908342","data":{"timestamp":" 946780908341"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780908596","data":{"timestamp":" 946780908596"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780909105","data":{"timestamp":" 946780909105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780909197","data":{"timestamp":" 946780909197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780910320","data":{"timestamp":" 946780910319"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780911869","data":{"timestamp":" 946780911869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYONG"," userResponse":" ILIYONG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780911937","data":{"timestamp":" 946780911937"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AA"," userResponse":" AA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780912463","data":{"timestamp":" 946780912463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780915205","data":{"timestamp":" 946780915205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780916282","data":{"timestamp":" 946780916281"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780917194","data":{"timestamp":" 946780917193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780920235","data":{"timestamp":" 946780920234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780920939","data":{"timestamp":" 946780920939"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780921546","data":{"timestamp":" 946780921546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780922526","data":{"timestamp":" 946780922525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780923532","data":{"timestamp":" 946780923531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780924254","data":{"timestamp":" 946780924254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780925146","data":{"timestamp":" 946780925146"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780928556","data":{"timestamp":" 946780928556"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780929223","data":{"timestamp":" 946780929222"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780929763","data":{"timestamp":" 946780929763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780930380","data":{"timestamp":" 946780930379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780933635","data":{"timestamp":" 946780933635"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780934498","data":{"timestamp":" 946780934498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780935710","data":{"timestamp":" 946780935710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZUILIWA"," userResponse":" ILIZUILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780936632","data":{"timestamp":" 946780936632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780937465","data":{"timestamp":" 946780937465"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780937589","data":{"timestamp":" 946780937589"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780938069","data":{"timestamp":" 946780938068"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780938298","data":{"timestamp":" 946780938298"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780938952","data":{"timestamp":" 946780938952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" MIIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780941672","data":{"timestamp":" 946780941672"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIA"," userResponse":" NILILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780943136","data":{"timestamp":" 946780943136"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780945298","data":{"timestamp":" 946780945297"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780946139","data":{"timestamp":" 946780946139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKULA"," userResponse":" SIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780946843","data":{"timestamp":" 946780946843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780947446","data":{"timestamp":" 946780947446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780947733","data":{"timestamp":" 946780947732"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780948606","data":{"timestamp":" 946780948604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780951609","data":{"timestamp":" 946780951608"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780952799","data":{"timestamp":" 946780952799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780953121","data":{"timestamp":" 946780953121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780954062","data":{"timestamp":" 946780954062"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780955358","data":{"timestamp":" 946780955357"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" ULITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780958870","data":{"timestamp":" 946780958870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ULIIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780959517","data":{"timestamp":" 946780959517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780960003","data":{"timestamp":" 946780960003"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780960493","data":{"timestamp":" 946780960493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780960999","data":{"timestamp":" 946780960998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780961444","data":{"timestamp":" 946780961444"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780961664","data":{"timestamp":" 946780961664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780962302","data":{"timestamp":" 946780962302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" MIIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780965419","data":{"timestamp":" 946780965419"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780966412","data":{"timestamp":" 946780966411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJARIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780967310","data":{"timestamp":" 946780967309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIVAA"," userResponse":" KUIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780967952","data":{"timestamp":" 946780967952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780968556","data":{"timestamp":" 946780968556"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780972098","data":{"timestamp":" 946780972098"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITABASAMU"," userResponse":" ULITABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780972464","data":{"timestamp":" 946780972463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780973657","data":{"timestamp":" 946780973656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780976328","data":{"timestamp":" 946780976327"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780976567","data":{"timestamp":" 946780976567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780977220","data":{"timestamp":" 946780977219"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUDI"," userResponse":" BUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780977657","data":{"timestamp":" 946780977656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILA"," userResponse":" ILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780979114","data":{"timestamp":" 946780979113"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTABASAMU"," userResponse":" KUTABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780979863","data":{"timestamp":" 946780979863"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780983134","data":{"timestamp":" 946780983134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780983326","data":{"timestamp":" 946780983325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780983985","data":{"timestamp":" 946780983985"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780984609","data":{"timestamp":" 946780984609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780985212","data":{"timestamp":" 946780985211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780986553","data":{"timestamp":" 946780986552"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780987749","data":{"timestamp":" 946780987748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780988636","data":{"timestamp":" 946780988636"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIPA"," userResponse":" ALINIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780989342","data":{"timestamp":" 946780989341"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780990139","data":{"timestamp":" 946780990139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780991563","data":{"timestamp":" 946780991562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDI"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780992586","data":{"timestamp":" 946780992586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYONG"," userResponse":" ILIYONG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780992604","data":{"timestamp":" 946780992604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARA"," userResponse":" ARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780993342","data":{"timestamp":" 946780993341"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANO"," userResponse":" MANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780995738","data":{"timestamp":" 946780995738"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780996912","data":{"timestamp":" 946780996912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIITUMA"," userResponse":" ULIITUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780998037","data":{"timestamp":" 946780998037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780998773","data":{"timestamp":" 946780998773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781002070","data":{"timestamp":" 946781002069"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781002671","data":{"timestamp":" 946781002671"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781003573","data":{"timestamp":" 946781003573"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781004521","data":{"timestamp":" 946781004521"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781004734","data":{"timestamp":" 946781004733"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781005537","data":{"timestamp":" 946781005536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781006630","data":{"timestamp":" 946781006629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVAA"," userResponse":" TULIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781007203","data":{"timestamp":" 946781007203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781007902","data":{"timestamp":" 946781007902"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781008820","data":{"timestamp":" 946781008820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781010635","data":{"timestamp":" 946781010634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATABASAMU"," userResponse":" TUKATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781013863","data":{"timestamp":" 946781013862"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TULIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781014565","data":{"timestamp":" 946781014565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781017978","data":{"timestamp":" 946781017977"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNADHANI"," userResponse":" UNADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781018504","data":{"timestamp":" 946781018504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781019765","data":{"timestamp":" 946781019764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAHITAJI"," userResponse":" LINAHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781020557","data":{"timestamp":" 946781020557"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781023786","data":{"timestamp":" 946781023786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIA"," userResponse":" KISIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781024004","data":{"timestamp":" 946781024004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781024608","data":{"timestamp":" 946781024607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781025326","data":{"timestamp":" 946781025325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781026229","data":{"timestamp":" 946781026229"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781027096","data":{"timestamp":" 946781027095"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEVAA"," userResponse":" NIMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781027608","data":{"timestamp":" 946781027607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781030407","data":{"timestamp":" 946781030406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781030513","data":{"timestamp":" 946781030513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781074429","data":{"timestamp":" 946781074428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" c1c830eb-d845-45b4-b7eb-50ad86bdbe1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781092580","data":{"timestamp":" 946781092579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" a5170085-e3a4-4e66-ab9c-6d0f39ce2fd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781095708","data":{"timestamp":" 946781095707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" a5170085-e3a4-4e66-ab9c-6d0f39ce2fd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781113722","data":{"timestamp":" 946781113721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054113"," gameId":" a5170085-e3a4-4e66-ab9c-6d0f39ce2fd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}